RG 062:134, Town of Stafford
Connecticut State Library
Town of Stafford records
1848-1979
Connecticut State Library
Stafford (Conn.)
21 cubic feet
Administrative, election, vital and tax records for the town of Stafford.
RG062_134
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Stafford was settled in 1719.
Scope and Content
Administrative, election, vital and tax records for the town of Stafford.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Connecticut. Justice of the Peace (Stafford)
Subjects:
Elections -- Connecticut -- Stafford -- Statistics; Voting -- Connecticut -- Stafford -- Statistics; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Stafford -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Stafford -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Stafford -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Stafford -- Registers; Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Stafford; Writs -- Connecticut -- Stafford
Places:
Stafford (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1848-1979
  - T000979
    - Individual tax lists
      Volumes for 1879-1881, 1883 are not boxed.
      - A - J, 1879; 1 volume
      - K - W, 1879; 1 volume
      - A - H, 1880; 1 volume
      - I - W, 1880; 1 volume
      - A - H, 1881; 1 volume
      - I - W, 1881; 1 volume
      - A - H, 1883; 1 volume
      - I - W, 1883; 1 volume
      - 1882, 1892 (Box Box 1)
    - Tax abstract, District 15, 1886 (Box Box 1)
    - Tax collector's book, 1896 (Box Box 1)
    - Vital records, 1886 (Box Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous town documents (Box Box 1)
    - Election returns, vouchers, writs, attachments, miscellaneous materials, 1848-1895 (Box Box 2)
    - Treasurer's order book (stubs only), 1879-1885 (Volume Item)
    - List of electors, 1886, 1894 (Map-case Map drawer 4)
    - Ballots, 1938 (Map-case Map drawer 4)
  - 2008-005
    - Tax abstracts
      These tax abstracts are not boxed.
      - 1913, 1 volume
      - 1914, 1 volume
      - 1915, 1 volume
      - 1916, 1 volume
      - 1917, 1 volume
      - 1918, 1 volume
      - 1919, 1 volume
      - 1920, 1 volume
      - 1921, 1 volume
      - 1922, 1 volume
      - 1923, 1 volume
      - 1924, 1 volume
      - 1925, 1 volume
      - 1926, 1 volume
      - 1927, 1 volume
      - 1928, 1 volume
      - 1929, 1 volume
      - 1930, 1 volume
      - 1931, 1 volume
      - 1932, 1 volume
      - 1933, 1 volume
      - 1934, 1 volume
      - 1935, 1 volume
      - 1936, 1 volume
      - 1937, 1 volume
      - 1938, 1 volume
      - 1939, 1 volume
      - 1940, 1 volume
      - 1941, 1 volume
      - 1942, 1 volume
      - 1943, 1 volume
      - 1944, 1 volume
      - 1945, 1 volume
      - 1946, 1 volume
      - 1947, 1 volume
      - 1948, 1 volume
      - 1949, 1 volume
      - 1950, 1 volume
      - 1951, 1 volume
      - 1952, 1 volume
      - 1953, 1 volume
      - 1954, 1 volume
      - Borough of Stafford, 1954; 1 volume
      - 1955, 1 volume
      - 1956, 1 volume
      - 1957, 1 volume
      - 1958, 1 volume
      - 1959, 1 volume
      - 1960, 1 volume
      - 1961, 1 volume
      - 1962, 1 volume
      - 1963, 1 volume
      - 1964, 1 volume
      - 1965, 1 volume
      - 1966, 1 volume
      - 1967, 1 volume
      - 1968, 1 volume
      - 1969, 1 volume
      - 1970, 1 volume
      - 1971, 1 volume
      - 1972, 1 volume
      - 1973, 1 volume
      - 1974, 1 volume
      - 1975, 1 volume
      - 1976, 1 volume
      - 1977, 1 volume
      - 1978, 1 volume
      - 1979, 1 volume